(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Tokoyami Towa 2nd Live *SHINier*
Attention
ご来場の皆様へ
To the Audience
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
二次販売グッズ
2nd Sales Merchandise
常闇トワ JACK!
Tokoyami Towa JACK!
あ！こっちこっちこっち！
Ah! Over here, over here, over here!
今日、二人じゃないんですね。
It's not just the two of you today, is it?
え、二人？さっきの、ここで会った人たち。
Eh, two? Oh, these people? I just met them here.
心で...
In my heart...
♪「ラヴ・パレード」 ORANGE RANGE
♪ "Love Parade" by ORANGE RANGE
Joyしてこうぜ！
Let's Joy together!
JOYSOUND X1
Tokoyami Towa 2nd Live *SHINier*
Tokoyami Towa 2nd Live "SHINier"
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
ARIAKE ARENA / 2025.10.29
ARIAKE ARENA / October 29, 2025
Attention / ご来場のお客様へ
Attention / To our guests
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering (loudly) is OK
二次販売グッズ
Second Round of Merchandise Sales
Tokoyami Towa 2nd Live "SHINier"
ARIAKE ARENA
2025.10.29
October 29, 2025
Attention
ご来場のお客様へ
To all visitors
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
声出し応援OKです
Due to production reasons, please beware of flashing lights.
Cheering loudly is OK.
二次販売グッズ
Secondary Sales Goods
Tokoyami Towa 2nd Live "SHINier"
ARIAKE ARENA 2025.10.29
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The content will be starting soon.
Attention - ご来場のお客様へ
Attention - To the audience
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
二次販売グッズ
Secondary Sales Goods
Tokoyami Towa 2nd Live *SHINier*
ARIAKE ARENA 2025.10.29
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention
ご来場のお客様へ
To all visitors
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK
二次販売グッズ
Secondary Sales Goods
受注販売期間
2025.10.22 20:00 - 2025.11.25 18:00
Order Period
Oct 22, 2025, 20:00 - Nov 25, 2025, 18:00
ERROR
鈍色の目の 涙命の色に滲んでいる
Dark grey eyes' tears are bleeding into the color of life
何を残して与えた 問いかけて潰れて
What did I leave behind and give? I ask and crumble.
青と赤と白を混ぜるこの世の真ん中で叫んでいる
Mixing blue, red, and white, I'm screaming in the middle of this world
何を求めて歩いた 追いかけて疲れて
What was I looking for as I walked? I chased and grew tired.
どのくらい以上 壊れているの?
How much more than this am I broken?
壊れているよ
I am broken
それでも息をしたい したい
Even so, I want to breathe, I want to.
君に見えてるの
Is it visible to you?
夢のように最後の言葉も詰まるよ
Like a dream, even my last words get stuck.
ERROR
遠い日の言葉 淡い光が空に溢れている
Words from a distant day, a faint light is overflowing in the sky
何を選んで並べた 涙色重ねて
What did I choose and line up? Overlapping the colors of tears.
浮かぶその体 意識の中 溶けて滲んでしまう
That floating body dissolves and bleeds into my consciousness
何を見てきて比べた 悲しくて忘れて
What have I seen and compared? Being sad and forgetting.
どのくらい以上 歪んでいるの?
How much more than this am I distorted?
歪んでいるよ
I am distorted
それでも息をしたい したい
Even so, I want to breathe, I want to.
夢を見ているの
I am dreaming
想う君に最後の言葉も詰まるよ
Thinking of you, even my last words get stuck.
ERROR
ERROR 404 NOT FOUND
与えることも失うことも
To give, or to lose
忘れることもできないの
I cannot even forget
暴れだすこのエラーを殺して
Kill this error that’s breaking loose
笑う僕がまた一人
And I'll be laughing alone again
壊しているの？
Am I breaking it?
壊して知るの？
Do I learn by breaking it?
それでも涙痛い痛い
Still, these tears hurt, they hurt
君に届いたの？
Did it reach you?
歌う声に最後の
In my singing voice, the final...
言葉並べても
even if I line up my words
重なる色滲んで
the overlapping colors blur
壊れているの？
Is it broken?
壊れているよ
It is broken
それでも息をしたいしたい
Still, I want to breathe, I want to breathe
君に見えてたの？
Was it visible to you?
夢のように最後の
Like a dream, the final...
言葉も詰まるよ
even my words get stuck
エラー...
Error...
乾いた虚しさと
With a parched emptiness
小さなこの空を
and this small sky
描いた
I drew it
彼方の色
The colors beyond
手を伸ばすほどに
The more I reach out my hand
歪むの
the more they distort
僕たちは何度も
We, time and again
問いかけて
keep questioning
灯火は迷わず照らすかな
I wonder if the lamp will shine without hesitation
まだ世界は目を閉じたまま
The world still has its eyes closed
やがて消えていくの？
Will it eventually disappear?
静かな暗闇と
With a quiet darkness
確かな感覚を
and a certain sensation
君の中の正義が
If the justice within you
灰がこぼれ落ちたら
spills out as ashes
全て試されて
everything is tested
見えないの
and I can't see it
抱いていたいもの
Things I want to hold dear
何度も失って
losing them time and again
この日々が夢であるなら
If these days are a dream
まだここから目を閉じたまま
still from here, with eyes closed
やがて消えて崩れていく
eventually disappearing and crumbling away
やめてよ
Stop it
揺れる感情を
these swaying emotions
壊して
break them
僕たちは過ちの中で
We, amidst our mistakes
何度も試されて
are tested time and again
まだ正義や愛と呼べるの
Can we still call it justice or love?
この世界は目を閉じたまま
This world, with its eyes still closed
やがて消えて崩れていく
eventually disappearing and crumbling away
風に吹かれて
Blown by the wind
誰も気づかぬよう
so that no one notices
区別がつかない
indistinguishable
モノクロの世界
a monochrome world
何一つ見えなくて
Unable to see anything
まるで私は
It was as if I...
息を止めていた
...was holding my breath.
もういいよ 遠くても
It's okay, even if it's far
叶えたい 私は
I want to fulfill it
こんな世界 想いも
Even in a world like this, these feelings...
抱きしめていたいのに
I want to hold them close, and yet...
夢のキャンバスに
On the canvas of my dreams
描き続ける意味は
The meaning of continuing to draw
この胸に輝いている
Is shining in my heart
Sorry
叶えることに意味などないけど
Fulfilling it has no meaning, but...
広いつめたい
A vast, cold...
駆け足夜の
...fast-paced night
そして夜は その冷たさを溶かして
And the night melts that coldness
手を伸ばした
And I reached out my hand
もういいよ 遠くても
It's okay, even if it's far
届けたい 私は
I want to reach out
受け止めて 涙も
Please accept them, even the tears
抱きしめていたいのに
I want to hold them close, and yet...
夢のキャンバスに
On the canvas of my dreams
心込めるのは
Putting my heart into it
この空に 描き出していく
I will draw it across this sky
Sorry
そして夜は その冷たさを溶かして
And the night melts that coldness
手を伸ばした
And I reached out my hand
もういいよ 遠くても
It's okay, even if it's far
叶えたい 私の
I want to fulfill it, my...
こんな世界 想いも
...feelings in a world like this
言葉で包んだ
I wrapped them in words
夢のキャンバスに
On the canvas of my dreams
彩を足していく
I'll add more color
この胸に 今輝いて
Now shining in my heart
強くなくてもいい
It's okay not to be strong
壊れかけてもいい
It's okay to be on the verge of breaking
この心は 永久に羽ばたいて
This heart will flap its wings forever
響くように 塗り替えていく
I will repaint it so it resonates
Palette
みんなー！
Everyone!
こやっぴー！常闇トワ様です！
Koya-ppi! This is Tokoyami Towa-sama!
あ、こやっぴーって返してくれるんだ。イェーイ！
Oh, you're replying with "Koya-ppi". Yay!
常闇トワ 2nd Live SHINier、いよいよ始まりました！
Tokoyami Towa 2nd Live "SHINier", it's finally started!
えー、ちょっとびっくりすると思うんですけども、
Um, I think you might be a bit surprised, but...
最初に「ERROR」を歌わせていただきました！
...first I sang "ERROR"!
びっくりした人ー？
Anyone surprised?
そうだよね、そうだよね、びっくりしますよね。
Right, right, it's surprising.
で、その後に「Twilight」と「Palette」を歌わせていただきました。
And after that, I sang "Twilight" and "Palette".
えー、やっぱりね、「ERROR」を...
Well, the reason I...
持ってきた理由なんですけれども...
...brought "ERROR"...
やっぱりね、まああの、「ERROR」を聴いて
I think there are many people...
常闇トワのことを知ってくれたみたいな人やっぱり、多いと思うんだよね。
...who came to know about Tokoyami Towa by listening to "ERROR".
そうだよね！多いからなんかちょっと、
Right! Since there are many, I thought...
エモいの持ってこようかなーみたいな感じで、
...I'd bring something emotional...
もうそんな感じで、コロッと、サラッと、決めちゃいました！
...and just like that, I decided on it quickly and easily!
なんか、結構最初の方に、
I think bringing a mellow song...
こう、しっとりする曲を持ってきたのは
...right at the beginning...
結構挑戦的だったのかなと思うんですけども。
...was quite a challenge.
どうでした？
How was it?
ありがとう。
Thank you.
え、みんなTシャツ着てくれてるやん！ありがとう！
Oh, everyone's wearing the T-shirts! Thank you!
ペンライトはね、あの、凶器にもなりかねないので
Be careful with the penlights, as they could...
気をつけてください。
...potentially become weapons.
いや、可愛いんだけどね、可愛いんだけどね。
I mean, they are cute, though.
前もいいけどちょっとあの、尖りすぎたっていう…
The previous one was good too, but it was a bit... too sharp...
まあ、そ、それもありますけども。思い出として残しておいてください。
Well, there's that too. Please keep it as a memory.
はい、そしてね、今回ライブなんですけれども
Yes, and so, for this live...
セカンドアルバムが『SHIN』というアルバムになっておりまして
The second album is named "SHIN"...
ま、ライブもね、その『SHIN』に沿って、
Well, the live too, following that theme of "SHIN"...
『SHINier』という風に付けさせていただいております。
I've named it "SHINier".
あの、歌はいいけど喋りが下手っていう、致命的に下手なんだけど大丈夫そうか？
Um, my singing is fine, but my talking is bad... like, fatally bad. Is it going to be okay?
あ、ありがとうございます、ありがとうございます。笑
Ah, thank you, thank you. lol
えー、このね、『SHINier』はね、えー、光るとか、輝くっていう意味があるのっで
Um, this "SHINier" has the meaning of "to shine" or "to sparkle"...
今日のライブは、来てくれてるみんなの心を
For today's live, I want to make it a performance that makes
輝かせるようなライブにしていきたいと思いまーす！
the hearts of everyone who came here shine!
えー、セカンドアルバムのね、楽曲もいっぱいあるので、お楽しみにしていてください。
Um, there are many songs from the second album too, so please look forward to it.
ありがとう。アルバムも買ってくれましたか？
Thank you. Did you also buy the album?
ありがとう。嬉しいです。
Thank you. I'm happy.
なんか今日も、ちょっとライブの前にエゴサしてたんですけども
You know, today too, before the live, I was ego-searching...
あの、いっぱい現地でも買いましたみたいな
Um, I saw many posts like "I bought it at the venue"
ポスカ、ポストカード、ゲットしましたみたいな感じで
or "I got the postcard" and things like that.
ツイートしてるのを見て、あ、ポストしてるのを見て、
I saw the tweets—I mean, posts—
すごい嬉しかったです。ははは。
and it made me really happy. Hahaha.
まだ慣れないんだよね、うん。えー、そして...
I'm still not used to it. Yeah. Um, and...
今日なんですけれども、ファーストと一緒で生バンドでやっております！
As for today, just like the first live, we're performing with a live band!
イェーイ、かっこよかったでしょ？
Yay, they were cool, right?
もう最初だけじゃないから。これからずっとかっこいいの演奏してくれます。
It's not just the beginning. They'll be playing cool music all the way through.
よろしくお願いいたします。
Please treat them well.
はい。えー、今日しか、なんと！今日しか聴けないライブアレンジが、ありありのアリなので
Yes. Um, today only... what! There are definitely live arrangements that you can only hear today...
このシーンで盛り上がってくれたら嬉しいです。はい。
so I'd be happy if you have fun and get excited. Yes.
そして、えー、今日は現地だけじゃなくて、配信もしております！
And, um, today is not just at the venue; we are also live-streaming!
なんと！ここら辺に手を振ると、
Look! If I wave my hand around here,
可愛いトワちゃんが、あの、インターネットを通して...
a cute Towa-chan will appear over the internet...
あ、ありがとうございます。ありがとうございます。はい、はい。あんまりそんな、あの、言われ慣れてないもんで。
Ah, thank you. Thank you. Yes, yes. I'm not really used to being told that.
はい。ありがとうございます。はい。
Yes. Thank you. Yes.
なんか色んなところにアピールしながらやってこうかなと思っております。
I'm thinking of performing while appealing to various places.
えー、そして今回の、えーハッシュタグなんですけれども
Um, and about today's hashtag...
ライブの感想をハッシュタグ『#常闇トワ2nd』でたくさんポストしてください！
please post many impressions of the live with the hashtag #常闇トワ2nd!
スクリーンショットOKっていうことなので、
Since screenshots are okay,
いっぱい、あの、ちょっといい、あの、盛れてる感じのでお願いいたします。
please take lots of... um, good ones, where I'm looking cute, please.
スクリーンショットして、あの投稿する場合は。はい。お願いいたします。
When you screenshot and post them. Yes. Please do.
そして、なんと。あ、これいつもの流れだから
And, guess what. Ah, you might know
分かっちゃうかもしれないけど、えー...
since it's the usual flow, but... um...
そうなんです。えー、YouTubeとTikTokでご覧の方は、
That's right. Um, for those watching on YouTube and TikTok,
ここまでとなっております。すみません！
this is the end for you. I'm sorry!
えーーー！」「お前ら『えー』じゃないだろ！いるだろ！
Ehhhh?! "Don't you guys 'Ehh' me! You're here, aren't you!
何が『えー』なんだよ！何に対しての『えー』なんだよ！
What are you 'Ehh'-ing for! What is that 'Ehh' even for!"
ね、あの、配信の見てくれてる人が『えー』っていう、あの代弁してくれたってことね。
Right, you're just speaking for the people watching the stream who are saying 'Ehh'.
そうだよね、そうだよね。ははは。はい。
That's it, right? I thought so. Hahaha. Yes.
はい。なのでね、えー、まだまだ一緒に盛り上がりたいみんなは、
Yes. So, um, everyone who wants to keep getting excited with me,
概要欄から配信サイトチェックして購入してくださいね。
please check the streaming site from the description box and purchase it.
ということで、次の曲、行こうかなと思うんですけども...
And so, I think I'll move on to the next song...
えー、まずちょっとアンケートを取りたいと思います。
Um, first I'd like to take a quick survey.
えー、本日、えー東京から来たよって方！
Um, today, who came from Tokyo?!
半分ぐらいかな？半分ぐらい。
About half? About half.
えー、じゃあ東京じゃないところから来た人！
Um, then, people who came from outside Tokyo!
むちゃくちゃ多いやん、むちゃありがとやん。
There's so many! Thanks a bunch.
えー、じゃあ... じゃあ北海道から来た人！
Um, then... how about people who came from Hokkaido!
いるやん！マジかよ、ありがとう。
There are some! Seriously? Thank you.
じゃあ沖縄から来たって人！
Then, anyone who came from Okinawa!
お、いるいるいるいる！ありがとう。ありがとう。
Oh, there are, there are! Thank you. Thank you.
ありがとう。はい。
Thank you. Yes.
えー、じゃあちょっと、あの、もっと拡大していいですか？
Um, then, can I expand the scope a bit more?
えー、日本じゃないところから来た人！
Um, anyone who came from outside Japan?!
おいおいおいむちゃくちゃいるじゃねーか！おおすごいすごい！ありがとう。
Hey hey hey, there's a ton of you! Oh wow, wow! Thank you.
えー、じゃあ、さらにむちゃくちゃ絞って、えー飛行機を...
Um, then, narrowing it down even further, um, those who used a plane...
12時間以上乗ってきた人？
Anyone who traveled for 12 hours or more?
えっ、いるやん！
Wait, there are actually people!
えっ、すごい！
Wait, that's amazing!
ありがとうございます。
Thank you so much.
ということで、なんか「わー」って今言えました？
So, were you able to shout just now?
まだ、でも足りないか。
But maybe it's still not enough.
じゃあ、トワ、掛け声しちゃおうかな？
Then, shall I give you a shout?
盛り上がれますかー！？
Can you get hyped!?
おー、結構最初なのに声出てるやん！
Oh, you're quite loud even though we just started!
なんか何回かやろうかなーって思ってたけど、結構声出てたけど。
I was thinking of doing it a few times, but you were already pretty loud.
ちょ、もう一回言っていいっすか？じゃあ。
Wait, can I say it one more time then?
盛り上がれますかー！？
Can you get hyped!?
うぉ〜！
Woah!
じゃあ、次の曲、いくぞー！LILIN！
Then, let's go to the next song! LILIN!
いくぞ、有明！
Let's go, Ariake!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!